spjimr.org 2019-08-06

# Privacy policy | SPJIMR

**Privacy Statement**

Thanks for visiting the website of the SP Jain Institute of Management & Research, Mumbai (SPJIMR). SPJIMR understands that the privacy of its users is important. Information collected on <http://www.spjimr.org/> is kept private and never shared with other organisations. We’re making this privacy statement to inform you about the types of information gathered and disseminated on the website. Please note that this policy has been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies continue to develop and evolve rapidly, and that such changes may require us to alter our Privacy Policy. Any such alterations will not affect our general commitment to the protection of our visitors’ privacy.

 **General Statement**

You may visit our website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. However, certain transactions that you choose to engage in on this site will require submission of your personal information, including, but not limited to, profile updates, applications and certain databases. As a general rule, SPJIMR will not sell, swap, rent, or otherwise disclose to any third party any such personal information for commercial purposes. Such information will be utilised only for the purpose stated. To accomplish such purpose, SPJIMR may disclose the information to its employees, consultants and agents who have a legitimate need to know the information. SPJIMR also reserves the right to disclose this information under special circumstances, including disclosures required by law, court order or circumstances under which disclosure, at the sole discretion of SPJIMR, is necessary to protect the legal rights, including the intellectual property rights, of SPJIMR.

 **Use of Information**

SPJIMR may collect other information about its users that is not connected with any specific personal identity, such as data about usage and service operation. The following summarises the types of information that we may collect.

System Information, IP Addresses and Referrers

When you connect to our website, our web server may record the numerical Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, information about your browser and operating system, date and time of access and the internet address and page which linked you to our web site. The staff of SPJIMR uses such information to diagnose problems, to administer and improve our website and to generate aggregate statistical reports that analyse general user information and demographics. Unless required by a legal process, we do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that user sessions may be tracked by IP address, but a user's identity remains anonymous.

In addition, we ordinarily do not disclose site usage to third parties by individual IP addresses, but may do so in very limited circumstances when complying with law or legal process, working with consultants assisting us in fixing or improving our site, or in monitoring and improving the security of our network. Our staff monitors search terms that users enter into our Search Engine, but this tracking is never associated with individual users.

 **Cookies**

Cookies are unique bits of computer data that many major websites will transfer to your computer the first time that you visit. Cookies are stored on your hard drive and may be later accessed by the website to track prior usage. SPJIMR may use cookies and pixels, or transparent GIF files. With both cookies and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. A cookie may also be used to deliver customizable and personalized services for information by tracking already visited pages. We may also use cookies to anonymously track session information, such as pages visited or duration of visit, which will help us continue to improve our format and content. You may be able to set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when one is being sent. It is likely that some portions of our site will not operate properly if cookies are disabled.

 **Security Precautions**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Unfortunately, due to the nature of Internet communications, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. While SPJIMR remains committed to protecting the privacy of our users, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. We do so by using secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access, however, we make no representations regarding the veracity of such measures.

 **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at [website.support@spjimr.org](mailto:website.support@spjimr.org)
